Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
- Box: 61, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 9: Soviet coal miners' union, 1979; Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
    Author: Evgenii Efremenko
  - Item 10: World Federation of Trade Unions at new stage, 1978; Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 11: World Federation of Trade Unions at new stage, 1978; Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 12: New generation of Soviet workers, 1973; Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
    Author: Valentina Spiridonovna Iazykova
  - Item 13: New generation of Soviet workers, 1973; Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Item 14: The working woman in the USSR, 1973; Publication (Box 61, Folder 23)
    Author: A.P. Biriukova
- Box: 61, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Kooperatsiav period diktatury proletariata., 1931; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Couctpax, 1932; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Trade unions within the political system of Soviet society, 1977; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
    Author: Evgenii Akimovich Ivanov
  - Item 4: Trade unions within the political system of Soviet society, 1977; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: The trade unions and the development of culture, 1977; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
    Author: Arnold Isaevich Arnoldov
  - Item 6: The international trade union movement, 1981; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
    Author: L.B. Moskvin
  - Item 7: Working class and socialist democracy, 1978; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
    Author: Viktor Sergeevich Shevtsov
  - Item 8: Unity is strength: Soviet Trade Unions in the struggle for unity in the International Workers' Movement, 1974; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
    Author: Yuri Arkadaksky
  - Item 9: Unity is strength: Soviet Trade Unions in the struggle for unity in the International Workers' Movement, 1974; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Item 10: USSR State Institutions Workers' Union, 1977; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
    Author: Georgii Andreevich Makeev
  - Item 11: Trade unions in the U.S.S.R., 1963; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
    Author: P.S. Petrov
  - Item 12: Our rising generation, 1977; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
    Author: S. Furin
  - Item 13: Our rising generation, 1977; Publication (Box 61, Folder 24)
- Box: 61, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: USSR trade union rules: endorsed by the 13th Congress of the Trade Unions of the USSR. Partially amended by the 14th Congress of teh Trade Unions of the USSR, March 4, 1968, the 15th Congress of teh Trade Unions of teh USSR, March 24, 1972, and the 16th, 1978; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
    Author: Vsesoiuznyi sezd professional'nykh soiuzov
  - Item 2: Freedom in the West: how human rights and trade union freedoms are violated, 1978; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
    Author: Vladimir Viktorovich Aleksandrov
  - Item 3: Freedom in the West: how human rights and trade union freedoms are violated, 1978; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Labour protection in the USSR, 1970; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
    Author: A.P. Semenov
  - Item 5: Labour protection in the USSR, 1970; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: The trade unions and the mass sport movement in the USSR, 1977; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
    Author: Vladimir Alekseevich Bogatikov
  - Item 7: The trade unions and the mass sport movement in the USSR, 1977; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 8: The well-being of the Soviet people, 1975; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
    Author: Yuri Kanin
  - Item 9: The well-being of the Soviet people, 1975; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 10: Social guarantees for every member of society, 1976; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
    Author: G.V. Budnikov
  - Item 11: Social guarantees for every member of society, 1976; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Item 12: Labour protection for the Soviet woman-worker, 1976; Publication (Box 61, Folder 25)
    Author: E.E. Novikova
- Box: 61, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1966; Publication (Box 61, Folder 26)
    Author: United Steelworkers of America
  - Item 2: Collective agreement for 1966 of the Krivoy Rog, Publication (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Study tour of USSR steel industry, October 3-11, 1966, Publication (Box 61, Folder 26)
    Author: United Nations. Economic Commission for Europe. Steel Committee
- Box: 61, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: All-Russian Union of Workers on Public Communications, 1920; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
    Author: Vserossiiskii? soiuz pochtovo-telegrafnykh rabochikh
  - Item 2: The role of trade unions in the state, economic and cultural life of the U.S.S.R., 1917-1959, 1960; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
    Author: Nikolai Prokhorovich Antropov
  - Item 3: Wages in the U.S.S.R., 1960; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
    Author: Leonid Alekseevich Kostin
  - Item 4: Labour legislation in the USSR, 1972; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
    Author: Soviet Union
  - Item 5: How labour disputes are settled in the Soviet Union, 1959; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
    Author: Ivan Dvornikov
  - Item 6: How labour disputes are settled in the Soviet Union, 1959; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: Mezhrabpom--organizator proletarskoi solidarnosti, 1931; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
    Author: Willi Munzenberg
  - Item 8: Trade union committees and production conferences in the U.S.S.R., 1959; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
    Author: Vsesoiuznyi tsentralnyi sovet professionalnykh soiuzov
  - Item 9: The Spiritual world of the Soviet worker, 1978; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
    Author: Nikolai Alexandrov
  - Item 10: Soviet women: their role in society, the economy, the trade unions, 1981; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Item 11: Trade unions and the development of physical culture and sports in the U.S.S.R., 1960; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
    Author: Aleksandr Stepanovich Vasilev
  - Item 12: The role of Soviet trade unions in housing and everyday services, 1961; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
    Author: Fedor Potashnikov
  - Item 13: Cultural and educational work of trade unions in the U.S.S.R., 1959; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
    Author: Vasilii Petrovich Il'in
  - Item 14: The Soviet Trade Unions, Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Item 15: A factory health centre, 1981; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Item 16: The right to housing in the USSR, 1979; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Item 17: The right to housing in the USSR, 1979; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Item 18: Armenian Artek Young Pioneer Camp, 1978; Publication (Box 61, Folder 27)
    Author: Akop Nalbandyan
- Box: 62, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade unions of the world in the struggle for workers' interests, 1980; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Author: M.V. Baglai?
  - Item 2: Trade unions of the world in the struggle for workers' interests, 1980; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Kak trudiahchiesiaSSSR uchastvuiu v upravlenii proizvodstvom, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Kak trudiahchiesiaSSSR uchastvuiu v upravlenii proizvodstvom, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Kak trudiahchiesiaSSSR uchastvuiu v upravlenii proizvodstvom, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Kak trudiahchiesiaSSSR uchastvuiu v upravlenii proizvodstvom, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Soviet trade unions today, 1980; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Soviet trade unions today, 1980; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: The right to work is guaranteed by law, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Author: Victor Glazyrin
  - Item 10: The working class and the socialist economic integration, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Author: Vladimir Sergeev
  - Item 11: The working class and the socialist economic integration, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Statute on the Standing Production Conference: approved by Decision No. 422 of USSR Council of Ministers and AUCCTU, of June 18, 1973, 1976; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: USSR-USA trade unions compared, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Author: George Morris
  - Item 14: Social fairness funds, 1980; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Author: B.V. Rakitskii
  - Item 15: The USSR, a workingman's land, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Author: Pedro Clavijo P.
  - Item 16: The Story of a worker's family, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: The Story of a worker's family, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Box: 62, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Lenin and the trade unions, 1970; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Author: Vasiliillich Prokhorov
  - Item 2: Lenin and the trade unions, 1970; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Arms build-up and disarmament, 1981; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Author: Aleksandr Efremovich Efremov
  - Item 4: The Party and the trade unions in the USSR, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Author: L.F. Fyodorov
  - Item 5: The Party and the trade unions in the USSR, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Rights of primary trade union organisation: basic documents, 1978; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: A look at the Soviet trade unions, 1983; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Author: F.E. Medvedev
  - Item 8: Children in the USSR, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Author: A.V. Fedulova
  - Item 9: Children in the USSR, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Ladder of harmonious growth, 1981; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Author: V.V. Kopeiko
  - Item 11: Ladder of harmonious growth, 1981; Publication (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Box: 62, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Arms build-up and disarmament, 1981; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: USSR trade union rules, 1978; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Rights of primary trade union organisation: basic documents, 1978; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: European security: social aspects, 1978; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: European security: social aspects, 1978; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Collective agreement in the USSR, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Author: Aleksei Mukhanov
  - Item 7: Collective agreement in the USSR, 1965; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Internationalism of socialist countries' unions, 1980; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Author: A. Loshchakov
  - Item 9: Internationalism of socialist countries' unions, 1980; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: When a conflict arises ...: How labour disputes are settled in the USSR, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Author: Yefim Ghershanov
  - Item 11: When a conflict arises ...: How labour disputes are settled in the USSR, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: USSR-USA trade unions compared, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Labour protection for the Soviet woman-worker, 1976; Publication (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Box: 62, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Trade unions of the world in the struggle for workers' interests, 1980; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Trade union committees and production conferences in the U.S.S.R.: powers and functions, 1959; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Author: Vsesoiznyi tsentralnyii sovet professionalnykh soiuzov
  - Item 3: Labour protection in the U.S.S.R., 1961; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Author: Anastasiia Nikolaevna Dementeva
  - Item 4: Report on the work of the All-Union Central Council of Trade Unions and the tasks of the Soviet trade unions arising out of the decisions of the 21st Congress of the C.P.S.U., 1959; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Author: V.V. Grishen
  - Item 5: Soviet trade unions and wages, 1959; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Author: Petur Petrov
  - Item 6: Pension system in the U.S.S.R., 1956; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Socialist emulation: initiative exploration estimation, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Author: Boris Bochkov
  - Item 8: Socialist emulation: initiative exploration estimation, 1979; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: A look at the Soviet Union, 1977; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: A look at the Soviet Union, 1977; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: A look at the Soviet Union, 1977; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: The working woman in the USSR, 1973; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: The working woman in the USSR, 1973; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: The working woman in the USSR, 1973; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Rest and leisure of the Soviet worker, 1976; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Author: Ivan Kozlov
  - Item 16: Rest and leisure of the Soviet worker, 1976; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Social insurance and the trade unions in the USSR, 1980; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Author: Robert Tsivilev
  - Item 18: Social insurance and the trade unions in the USSR, 1980; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: Role of Soviet trade unions in production, 1959; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Trade Unions in the U.S.S.R., 1958; Publication (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Author: Exposition universelle et internationale
- Box: 62, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The rules of the trade unions of the USSR, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The rules of the trade unions of the USSR, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: A look at the Soviet trade unions, 1983; Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: How Soviet working people participate in production management, Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: How Soviet working people participate in production management, Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: The Soviet Trade Unions, Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: The Soviet Trade Unions, Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: The target: Trade unions, 1983; Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
    Author: I U Gvozdev
  - Item 9: Why there are jobs for all in the USSR, 1984; Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Why there are jobs for all in the USSR, 1984; Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: The Work collective's plenipotentiary: about VEF's factory union, 1980; Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: The Work collective's plenipotentiary: about VEF's factory union, 1980; Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: In the working man's interests, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
    Author: Nikolai Trofimyuk
  - Item 14: In the working man's interests, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Box: 62, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Trade unions in the Soviet political system, 1984; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Author: Evgenii Ivanov
  - Item 2: Report on AUCCTU activity and the tasks of Soviet trade unions in the light of the decisions of the 26th CPSU Congress, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Author: S.A. Shalaev
  - Item 3: Report on AUCCTU activity and the tasks of Soviet trade unions in the light of the decisions of the 26th CPSU Congress, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Social insurance and concern for peoples health in the USSR, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Social insurance and concern for peoples health in the USSR, Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Sea and River Workers' Union, 1976; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Author: Georgi Oleshkevich
  - Item 7: Sea and River Workers' Union, 1976; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: How Soviet trade unions look after workers' interests, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Author: B.A. Shelomov
  - Item 9: How Soviet trade unions look after workers' interests, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: For the People's well-being, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Author: Albert Demchenko
  - Item 11: For the People's well-being, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: The USSR society of inventors and innovations, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: The USSR society of inventors and innovations, 1982; Publication (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Box: 62, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Soviet trade unions, 1985; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: The African working class and trade unions, 1988; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: Alla Oganova
  - Item 3: Act before it's too late, 1984; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Act before it's too late, 1984; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: The target: Trade unions, 1983; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: I.U. Gvozdev
  - Item 6: The optimism of builders of a new world, 1983; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: Victor Andriyanov
  - Item 7: The optimism of builders of a new world, 1983; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Socialist economic integration and the trade unions, 1985; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: V.E. Sergeev
  - Item 9: Socialist economic integration and the trade unions, 1985; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Socialist economic integration and the trade unions, 1985; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: The heavy burden of militarism, 1986; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Author: Gennadi Nikolaev
  - Item 12: The heavy burden of militarism, 1986; Publication (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Box: 62, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Trade unions in the Soviet political system, 1984; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Trade unions in the Soviet political system, 1984; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Trade unions versus giant corporations, 1986; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Author: Stal Aleksandrovich Ershov
  - Item 4: Trade unions versus giant corporations, 1986; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Trade unions versus giant corporations, 1986; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: The heavy burden of militarism, 1986; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Where safety on the job is guaranteed by law, 1984; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Where safety on the job is guaranteed by law, 1984; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: The city where we live, 1984; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Author: Valerii Vyzhutovich
  - Item 10: The city where we live, 1984; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Benefits for one and all: the social consumption funds in the USSR, 1985; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
    Author: Georgi Sarkisyan
  - Item 12: Benefits for one and all: the social consumption funds in the USSR, 1985; Publication (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Box: 62, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: 1941-1945, our victory, 1985; Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Author: Konstantin Shishkov
  - Item 2: 1941-1945, our victory, 1985; Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: The policy of peace and unity, 1984; Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: The policy of peace and unity, 1984; Publication (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Box: 63, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New directions in European unionism: with some implications for American unions, 1971; Publication (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Author: Everett M. Kassalow
- Box: 63, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: La CTV: Historia y Lucha // The CTV: History and struggle, Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: 40 Anos de la C.T.U.: 1935-1976, Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: 40 Anos de la C.T.U.: 1935-1976, Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: 40 Anos de la CTV, 1977; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Author: Vargas, Jose
  - Item 5: Perfiles, 1975; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.34
  - Item 6: Perfiles, 1975; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.40
  - Item 7: Perfiles, 1975; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.47
  - Item 8: Perfiles, 1975; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.48
  - Item 9: Perfiles, 1975; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.49
  - Item 10: Perfiles, 1975; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.51
  - Item 11: Perfiles, 1975; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.54
  - Item 12: Perfiles, 1975; Publication (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.55
- Box: 63, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Contrato colectivo de trabajo -- 1974-1977, Publication (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Box: 63, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Contrato Colective de Trabajo, 1970; Publication (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Box: 63, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Hiep-Uoc Xi-Nghiep, 1965; Publication (Box 63, Folder 5)
    Language: Vietnamese.
  - Item 2: Hiep-Uoc Xi-Nghiep, 1965; Publication (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Labor agreement between ESSO Standard Eastern, Inc. and Viet-Nam Petroleum Workers' Union: 1965 = Thoa-Uoc Lao-Dong giva ESSO Standard Eastern, Inc. va Nghiep-Doan Cong-Nhan Hang Dau Viet-Nam, Publication (Box 63, Folder 5)
    Author: ESSO Standard Eastern, Inc.; Viet-Nam Petroleum Workers' Union
  - Item 4: Labor agreement between ESSO Standard Eastern, Inc. and Viet-Nam Petroleum Workers' Union: 1965 = Thoa-Uoc Lao-Dong giva ESSO Standard Eastern, Inc. va Nghiep-Doan Cong-Nhan Hang Dau Viet-Nam, Publication (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Box: 63, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Workers manage factories in Yugoslavia, 1950; Publication (Box 63, Folder 6)
    Author: Josip Broz Tito
- Box: 63, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Glossary, Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Confederation of trad unions of Yugoslavia, Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Mos?a Pijade Workers' University and workers' education, 1965; Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Author: Vlado Velcic
  - Item 4: Le syste`me de delegations, 1977; Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Author: Miodrag Dj Zecevic
  - Item 5: Social plan of Yugoslavia, 1976-1980, Publication (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Author: Yugoslavia. Skupstina
- Box: 63, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Anti-Monopolist conference of Oil Workers of the Mediterranean. The Black Sea and the Middle East, Publication (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Anti-Monopolist conference of Oil Workers of the Mediterranean. The Black Sea and the Middle East, Publication (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Anti-Monopolist conference of Oil Workers of the Mediterranean. The Black Sea and the Middle East, Publication (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Box: 63, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The trade union movement and the public sector, 1981; Publication (Box 63, Folder 9)
    Author: Council of Nordic Trade Unions
  - Item 2: Guiding lines for Nordic trade unions work with computing issues, 1976; Publication (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Programme on family policy, 1976; Publication (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Council of Nordic Trade Unions: the Nordic Trade Union Movement and the International Economic Policy, Publication (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Programme on social policy, 1979; Publication (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Programme of action concerning multinational companies, 1979; Publication (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Box: 63, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: ETIC Consumer programme, Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
    Author: European Trade Union Confederation
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1973; Publication (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Box: 63, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Role of industrial policy in Western Europe: a trade union perspective, 1987; Publication (Box 63, Folder 11)
    Author: European Trade Union Institute